(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
ChocoLove
作詞・作曲 Junky
Lyrics & Composition: Junky
聞いて　会いたい気持ち飛んでって
Listen, my feelings of wanting to see you fly away
すごく　まあるいくらいにおねだり
I'm begging you, with a big, round heart
ねぇちょっと聞いてみて受け取って
Hey, just listen to me and accept it
甘くとろけちゃうようなトキめきを
This sweet, melting heart-flutter
疲れてる顔して　いつもたくさん頑張ってるね
You look tired, you've always been working so hard
もうすべて任せて　全部食べてあげようか
Leave everything to me now, shall I eat it all up?
よそ見なんて嫌だよ　ちゃんとこっち向いていなくちゃ
I don't like you looking away, you have to look right at me
目と目が合うでしょ　照れちゃうくらい見つめてね
Our eyes meet, don't they? Stare at me until I blush
ひとつ　夢中にさせて
One, make me go crazy for you
ふたつ　見つけてね
Two, please find me
とりこ　虜にしちゃうの
I'll make you fall for me completely
心拍　急上昇
My heart rate is skyrocketing
好きよ
I love you
痛いの痛いの飛んでって
Pain, pain, go away
不安な顔より笑顔見せて
Show me a smile instead of an anxious face
ねぇちょっと聞いてみて受け取って
Hey, just listen to me and accept it
甘いチョコのようなトキめきを
This sweet, chocolate-like heart-flutter
ここに痛いの痛いのもう困っちゃう
The pain is right here, it's so troubling
不意打ちにちょこっとトキめくの
Getting a little heart-fluttered by a surprise
開いちゃうわよだめもうちょっと
It's going to open, no, just a bit more
君の声をもっと聴かせて
Let me hear more of your voice
不安なんて抱えてらしくないなんて思ってた
I thought holding onto anxiety wasn't like me
全部全部まるごと包み込んで溶かしてあげる
I'll wrap everything, everything up and melt it away
どうしたって　何したって
No matter what, no matter what I do
気持ちは同じなんだよね
Our feelings are the same, aren't they?
ここだって　そこだって
Whether it's here or there
想いは伝わるから
Because my feelings will reach you
声にして　文字にして
Put them into words, put them into writing
勇気出して伝えてよ
Pluck up your courage and tell me
強がって　意地はって
Stop acting tough and being stubborn
愛してよ
Just love me
隠さないでちゃんとおしえて
Don't hide it, tell me properly
君のこと全部を頂戴
Give me every single part of you
頂戴
Give it to me
聞いて　会いたい気持ち飛んでって
Listen, my feelings of wanting to see you fly away
すごく　まあるいくらいにおねだり
I'm begging you, with a big, round heart
高鳴る...
My heart is thumping...
聞いてみて
Please listen
感じてほしいの
I want you to feel it
会いたいわすぐ飛んでって
I want to see you, I'll fly to you right away
少し困るくらいおねだり
Pleading just a little too much
ちゃんと聞いてみて受け取って
Please listen carefully and receive it
甘くとろけちゃうようなときを
A time that's so sweet it melts
隣にいたいから
Because I want to be by your side
みんなー！
Everyone!
今日はチョコのお誕生日ライブ来てくださって
Thank you for coming to Choco's birthday live today!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
見てるー？
Are you watching?
いやね、実はね、
Well, actually,
歌だけの3Dライブは実は初めてなんだけど
it's actually my first time doing a 3D live with only singing,
一生懸命練習して、歌って踊って、
but I practiced really hard, singing and dancing,
みんなと最後まで楽しめたら、チョコすごい嬉しいな！
and if I can enjoy it with everyone until the end, Choco would be so happy!
へへっ！
Hehe!
なんと今回はゲストのみんなに行ってもらったり
And this time, I'll have some guests...
最後に重大告知があるので、
And there's a major announcement at the end,
ぜひお楽しみに！
so please look forward to it!
それでは、次の曲は、
Now, for the next song,
実はね...
actually...
次は、以前Twitterで
For the next one, I previously
チョコに歌ってほしい曲をリクエスト欲しい！ってツイートしたの
posted on Twitter asking for song requests you want Choco to sing.
ツイート覚えてるみんな？
Do you all remember that tweet?
覚えてるかな？
Do you remember?
なんと、そのリクエスト曲の中からチョコ選んじゃった！
I actually chose from those requested songs!
ちょっと噛んだのは気にしないで！
Don't mind me stumbling over my words a bit!
はい、ということで、
Yes, so,
何が選ばれたのか予想してみてね。
try to guess what was chosen.
ねえ、何だと思う？何だと思う？
Hey, what do you think? What do you think?
ふむふむ、なるほどね。うんうん。
Hmm, I see. Yeah, yeah.
さあ、みんなの正解は当たってるのかー！
Now, let's see if your answers are correct!
正解はこの曲です。
The correct answer is this song.
Moonlight shadow
ひとりぼっち
All alone
喉が渇いてただけなのよ
I was just thirsty
囓り付いた
I bit into it
囓る甘い病も毒だ
The sweet sickness I bite is also poison
侵された
I've been tainted
Black Cherry 濡れた
Black Cherry, soaked
堕ちて私の中へ
Falling into me
種を残し 蘇れ
Leave the seed and be reborn
愛してくれなくていいよ
You don't have to love me
愛してないから
Because I don't love you
これ以上惨めにさせないで
Don't make me any more miserable
二人のこのヒストリー
This history of ours
ちょっとした寄り道なの
is just a little detour
心はまだミステリー
My heart is still a mystery
抱かれた夜の数だけ流した涙
Tears shed for as many nights as I was held
紅いルージュ シャツの跡
Red rouge, marks on the shirt
言葉を飲み込み口付ける
Swallowing the words and kissing
苦いシャワー 私じゃない香り知らない
A bitter shower, I don't know the scent that isn't mine
押し殺し麻痺
Suppressing it and getting paralyzed
またエクスタシー Dirtyな最高
Ecstasy again, a dirty high
折れた羽を震わせながら
While trembling my broken wings
止めなきゃだ 噛みしめた唇
I have to stop it, my bitten lips
スローモーション飲み込まれ
Being swallowed in slow motion
Don't kiss me 離れないで
Don't kiss me, don't leave me
Don't kiss me でも許せない
Don't kiss me, but I can't forgive you
...down
Black Cherry 濡れて 落ちて 私の中へ
Black Cherry, getting wet, falling into me
種を残して yeah
Leaving your seed, yeah
愛さなくていいよ 愛せないから
You don't have to love me, because you can't
こんなに惨めにして yeah
Make me miserable like this, yeah
禁断の手口 ずっと抜け出せなくなって
A forbidden trick, I can't escape it anymore
感じる Black Cherry キスの感触 ちょっと忘れられない
I feel the Black Cherry, the feel of your kiss, I can't quite forget it
Don't stop kiss me 離れられない
Don't stop kiss me, I can't leave you
Don't stop kiss me でも許せない
Don't stop kiss me, but I can't forgive you
中に出して
Put it inside
Black Cherry 濡れて 落ちて 私の中へ
Black Cherry, getting wet, falling into me
種を残して yeah
Leaving your seed, yeah
愛さなくていいよ 愛せないから
You don't have to love me, because you can't
こんなに惨めにして yeah
Make me miserable like this, yeah
Black Cherry 頂戴 Black Cherry もっと
Give me Black Cherry, Black Cherry, more
本当はずっと 愛してたのに
Even though I had actually loved you all along
短いヒストリー ちょっとした寄り道なの
A short history, just a little detour
これでバイバイ
This is goodbye
消えるたまには こんな私のこと思い出して
Fade away, once in a while, please remember me
ひとりごとだよ
It's just a monologue
恥ずかしいこと聞かないでよね
Don't ask about embarrassing things
キミのことだよ
It's about you
でもその先は言わないけどね
But I won't say any more than that
ヒトリゴト 作詞：ケリー 作曲：神前 暁 編曲：高橋 浩一郎
Hitorigoto Lyrics: Kelly Composition: Satoru Kosaki Arrangement: Koichiro Takahashi
掛け違えてる ボタンみたいな もどかしさを
Like buttons fastened incorrectly, this frustration...
ほどけないまま また難しくしようとしてる
Remaining untied, I'm trying to make it difficult again
伝えたい気持ちは今日も 言葉になる直前に
The feelings I want to convey, today too, right before they become words...
変換ミスの連続で ため息と一緒に飲み込んだら
In a series of conversion errors, if I swallow them with a sigh...
ほろ苦い...
It's bittersweet...
ふとした瞬間に探しているよ
In a casual moment, I'm looking for you
キミの笑顔を探しているよ
I'm looking for your smile
無意識の中 その理由は まだ言えないけど
In my subconscious, the reason for that, I can't say it yet
一人でいると会いたくなるよ
When I'm alone, I miss you
誰といたって会いたくなるよ
No matter who I'm with, I miss you
たった一言 ねえ、どうしても...
Just one word, hey, no matter what...
言えないその言葉
I can't say those words
言えないこの気持ち...
I can't say these feelings...
早く気づいてほしいのに
Even though I want you to notice soon
1000ピースあるパズルみたいな選択肢と
With options like a 1,000-piece puzzle
想像力が判断力の邪魔をしちゃう
Imagination gets in the way of judgment
掴めない気持ちは今日も 可愛くない顔見せて
These elusive feelings, today too, show an uncute face
自己嫌悪プラス後悔で 溜め込んだ「ごめんね」を吐き出すには
With self-loathing plus regret, to spit out the 'sorry' I've bottled up...
ほど遠い...
It's far from it...
耳を澄ませば聞こえてくるよ
If I listen closely, I can hear it
キミの声だけ聞こえてくるよ
I can hear only your voice
雑踏の中 気づかないふり しているけど
In the bustle, I'm pretending not to notice, but...
隣にいると嬉しくなるよ
When you're next to me, I get happy
遠くにいると寂しくなるよ
When you're far away, I get lonely
単純なこと でもどうしても...
It's simple, but no matter what...
言えないその言葉
I can't say those words
言えないこの気持ち...
I can't say these feelings...
もっと素直に...
Be more honest...
なりたい
I want to be...
泣き出しそうな 空模様
The sky looks like it's about to cry.
頬にひとつぶ 雨かな
Is that a drop of rain on my cheek?
ねえ 今 心 飾る 隠した
Hey, now, I've hidden the decorations in my heart.
独り言に 全部 隠した
I've hidden it all in my soliloquy.
君のこと 本当はずっと
The truth is, about you, always...
ああ
Ah...
ふとしたときに 探しているよ
I find myself looking for you at unexpected moments.
君の笑顔を 探しているよ
I'm looking for your smile.
無意識の中 その理由は まだ 消えないけど
Even though the reason within my subconscious hasn't vanished yet.
ひとりでいると 会いたくなるよ
When I'm alone, I want to see you.
誰といたって 会いたくなるよ
No matter who I'm with, I want to see you.
たったひと言 ねえ どうして
Just a single word, hey, why?
言えない その言葉
I can't say those words.
言えない この気持ち
I can't say these feelings.
早く 気付いてほしいのに
Even though I want you to notice soon...
みんなー、僕たちの『高性能プリ』見てくれたー？
Everyone, did you see our "High-spec Puri"?
チョロも二人揃ったら、ヘッポコ性能じゃないって分かってくれたんじゃないかしら？
I hope you realized that when both Choro are together, we're not "clumsy performance"?
え、先生、それって僕一人だと高性能じゃないってこと？
Eh, Sensei, does that mean I'm not high-performance when I'm alone?
んー、何も聞こえない。
Hmm, I can't hear anything.
ねえ、おいおいおいおい！
Hey, wait, wait, wait, wait!
まあまあ、でも、今日は先生の誕生日だから、許してあげようかな。
Well, well, but since today is Sensei's birthday, I guess I'll forgive you.
いー、やったー。
Yay!
そういえばロボ子、気付いてた？
By the way, Roboco, did you notice?
ん？ 何？
Hmm? What?
3Dで二人だけでチョロをやるの、実は初めてなんだよ。
Doing "Choro" with just the two of us in 3D is actually a first.
え？ ガチ？
Eh? Seriously?
ガチ。
Seriously.
ちょっと、ちょっと、離れないでよ。ちょっと、ガチで離れないで。
Hey, hey, don't move away. Hey, seriously, don't move away.
え、撮って、え、ガチ撮ってないんだけどなー。
Eh, taking screenshots, eh, I really haven't taken any yet.
え、ってことは、もし今が、みんなが二人3Dのチャンスってこと？
Eh, so does that mean, maybe right now is everyone's chance for the two of us in 3D?
こと？
Thing?
こと！
Thing!
いやー、皆様、チョロでいっぱい撮っちゃってください！
Wow, everyone, please take lots of screenshots of Choro!
先生、どんなポーズとる？ どんなポーズとる？
Sensei, what pose should we do? What pose should we do?
どうしよう、どうしよう。えーじゃあ、最初は、じゃあ、てぇてぇポーズとりたいから、
What should we do, what should we do? Well, then, for the first one, since I want to do a "te-te-" pose...
ちょっとロボ子、ちょっとチョコの前に来なさいよ、ほらほらほらほら。
Roboco, come in front of Choco, come on, come on.
あれ？ これってもしかして...
Oh? Is this perhaps...?
じゃ、チョコが後ろから...
Then, Choco from behind...
ぎゅー！先生、ちょっといつもやってること！
Hug! Sensei, hey, this is what you always do!
おら、ちょ、おい！ 何を、おい、ちょっ...
Hey, wait, hey! What... hey, wait...
もうちょっと照れろよ！ いつもやってることじゃねーだろ、おい！
Be a bit more embarrassed! It's not like we always do this, hey!
せっかくチョコがちょっと後ろからぎゅーってしてあげたのに、もう。
After I went through the trouble of giving you a hug from behind, geez.
皆さん、これが日常です、僕たちの。
Everyone, this is our everyday life.
しっかり見届けよう。
Let's keep a close watch on it.
まあね。
I guess so.
ロボ子の家ではね、まあ、こうしてることも多いですよね。
At Roboco's house, well, we do this often, don't we?
いや、じゃあそこ先生の抱き枕になってあげようかなロボ子、ほら来いよ、ほら来いよ。
No, then maybe I'll become Sensei's body pillow here, Roboco. Come here, come here.
しょうがないな、ほら。
Can't be helped, then.
ぎゅー！
Hug!
じゃあ、二つ目のポーズは、
Then, for the second pose...
ロボ子ありあり！ サムネサムネ！
Roboco's definitely in! Thumbnail, thumbnail!
サムネ、あ、これ。しょうがないわ、でも。任せてよ。
Thumbnail, ah, this. Can't be helped, then. Leave it to me.
まずは背中合わせになって。
First, stand back-to-back.
はい！
Yes!
では口元に指を持って行って...
Then, bring your finger to your mouth...
こうして、こんな感じかな。
Like this, something like this?
結構、え、結構いい。ちょ、カメラさん、寄ってもらっていいですか？
Quite, eh, quite good. Hey, Cameraman, can you zoom in?
え、ちょっと離れるなよ！ ちょっと、チョコ、近付け、近付けて近付いて。
Eh, don't move away! Hey, Choco, get closer, get closer and closer.
遠くない？ ちょっとカメラさん、ああ！
Isn't it too far? Hey, Cameraman, ah!
すごーい！
Amazing!
いい。
Good.
これでサムネポーズを、ご、
With this, the thumbnail pose is...
っこん！
Kkon!
みんな、今がスクショタイムだぞ、撮れ撮れ撮れ撮れ。
Everyone, now is the screenshot time, take them, take them, take them.
そうだぞ、そうだぞ！
That's right, that's right!
オッケーかな。
Is it okay now?
あーどう、これ、ウインクまでしちゃうわ。
Ah, how about this, I'll even wink.
え、ずるい、チョコもウインクしよ。
Eh, no fair, Choco will wink too.
ねえ、先生、待って、こんなポーズやっちゃったらロボ子さ、先生のセクシー講座受けたいなー。
Hey, Sensei, wait, after doing this kind of pose, I want to take Sensei's sexy lecture.
え、ロボ子セクシーポーズできるの？
Eh, Roboco, can you do sexy poses?
それをやるのが先生の役目だろ！
Teaching that is Sensei's job, right!
もう、しょうがないな。はい、じゃあ。
Geez, can't be helped. Okay, then.
ロボ子、ほら、屈んで。
Roboco, look, bend down.
屈んで、屈んで。オッケーオッケー。
Bending down, bending down. Okay, okay.
ちょっと膝曲げてもらって。
Bend your knees a little.
屈んで、屈んで、待って、もうちょっとやばくない？ まあいっか。際どいよね。
Bending down, bending down... wait, isn't this a bit risky? Oh well. It's quite risky, isn't it?
で、腰をクィッと。
And, flick your hips.
クィッと。
Flick.
クィッとして、あーいい、いい。
Flick them, ah, nice, nice.
で、脇を見たいから、両腕上げちゃって。
And, because I want to see your armpits, raise both arms.
待って、これお前の趣味入ってるだろ！お前の趣味入ってるだろが！
Wait, your own fetish is leaking into this, isn't it! Your fetish is leaking into this!
あら。
Oh my.
しょうがない、じゃあチョコがお手本見せてあげるから、ちゃんとそれ通りやって、ロボ子。
Can't be helped, then Choco will show you an example, so do it exactly like that, Roboco.
はい、早くして。
Yes, hurry up.
じゃ、まずは片足をちょっと曲げて。
Then, first, bend one leg slightly.
ちょっと曲げて。
Bend it slightly.
で、腰をちょっとクィッとして。
And, flick your hips slightly.
クィッとして。
Flick them.
で、両腕を上げて脇を見せる。
And, raise both arms and show your armpits.
ちょっとセクシーな流し目みたいにして。
Make a slightly sexy sidelong glance.
まって！
Wait!
あ、いい！いい！やばい！
Oh, nice! Nice! This is crazy!
エチセクシーじゃない？あ、やばい、どう？
Isn't it lewdly sexy? Oh, man, how's this?
そこですカメラマンさん！二人でセクシーポーズ！
Right there, Mr. Cameraman! A sexy pose from the two of them!
うわああ！セクシー！みんな今だ、今がスクショタイムですよ！
Whoa! Sexy! Everyone, now's the time! It's screenshot time!
ああ、どう？はい、カメラさん！あ、ここが一番セクシーかもしれない！
Ah, how is it? Yes, camera-san! Ah, this might be the sexiest part!
いいですよ！いいですよ！
Looking good! Looking good!
ちょっとカメラさん寄ってください！寄って寄って寄って！
Camera-san, please zoom in a bit! Closer, closer, closer!
グイグイグイ！セクシー！わたくしたちセクシー！
Zooming right in! Sexy! We are so sexy!
セクシー！どうこれ？どうかしら？
Sexy! How's this? What do you think?
やばい、ロボ子先生になっちゃう！
Oh no, she's turning into Roboco-sensei!
うわ、ふふ、ロボ子先生だわ。
Whoa, hehe, she really is Roboco-sensei.
いいわよ。ロボ子先生だって、みんな！
It's fine. She's Roboco-sensei, everyone!
ああ、みんな可愛く撮ってくれたかな？くれたかな？
Ah, I wonder if everyone got some cute shots? I wonder?
じゃあ先生はこのあともあると思うから、引き続き頑張ってください。
Well, Sensei, I think you have more to do later, so please keep up the good work.
ありがとうロボ子！バイバーイ！
Thank you, Roboco! Bye-bye!
バイバーイ！
Bye-bye!
セクシーな感じ、バイバイ！
Keep that sexy vibe, bye-bye!
セクシーロボ子バイバイ！
Bye-bye, sexy Roboco!
お疲れ様！またね！
Great job! See ya!
バイバーイ！
Bye-bye!
チェリボム
Cherry Bomb
弾けてもっと熟して
Pop and ripen more
どこまでも私を愛して　チェリチェリボム
Love me forever, Cherry Cherry Bomb
弾けてもっと熟してね
Pop and ripen more, okay?
あちゅくちゅく　チェリチェリボム
A-chu-ku-chu-ku, Cherry Cherry Bomb
チェリチェリボム
Cherry Cherry Bomb
真っ赤に染まった　チェリハ　衝撃的なほどにうぶな
The cherry heart dyed bright red, so innocent it's shocking
いわゆる初恋みたいな恋
A love that's like what they call first love
どうにかなっちゃいそうよ　チェリハ　爆発的に魅力的な君は
I feel like I'm going crazy, cherry heart, you who are explosively attractive
私を虜にしたの　キュンとしちゃうでしょ
Have captivated me, it makes your heart skip a beat, right?
キュンとしちゃうでしょ
It makes your heart skip a beat, right?
突っつかれすぎて　もっともっと真っ赤になっちゃうの
Poked too much, I'm turning more and more red
弾けてもっと熟して
Pop and ripen more
どこまでも私を愛して　チェリチェリボム
Love me forever, Cherry Cherry Bomb
弾けてもっと熟してね
Pop and ripen more, okay?
あちゅくちゅく　チェリチェリボム
A-chu-ku-chu-ku, Cherry Cherry Bomb
チェリチェリボム
Cherry Cherry Bomb
トロトロトロトロ来ちゃう　私の1番弱いとこ
It's melting, melting, coming to my weakest spot
もうどうにかなっちゃいそうよ　チェリーハート
I feel like I'm going crazy already, Cherry Heart
ソワソワソワソワしちゃう　あなたの1番弱いとこ
It's making me restless, your weakest spot
どうにかしてあげるわ
I'll do something about it
キュンとしちゃうでしょ　突っつかれすぎて
It makes your heart skip a beat, right? Poked too much
もっともっと真っ赤になっちゃうの
I'm turning more and more red
弾けてもっと熟して
Pop and ripen more
絶対的に私を愛して　チェリチェリボム
Love me absolutely, Cherry Cherry Bomb
弾けてもっと熟してね
Pop and ripen more, okay?
あちゅくちゅく　チェリチェリボム
A-chu-ku-chu-ku, Cherry Cherry Bomb
男の子も
Boys too
（チェリボム！チェリボム！）
(Cherry Bomb! Cherry Bomb!)
女の子も
Girls too
（チェリボム！チェリボム！）
(Cherry Bomb! Cherry Bomb!)
男の子も
Boys too
（チェリボム！チェリボム！）
(Cherry Bomb! Cherry Bomb!)
女の子も
Girls too
（チェリボム！チェリボム！）
(Cherry Bomb! Cherry Bomb!)
男の子も
Boys too
（チェリボム！チェリボム！）
(Cherry Bomb! Cherry Bomb!)
女の子も
Girls too
（チェリボム！チェリボム！）
(Cherry Bomb! Cherry Bomb!)
チェリボム！チェリボム！チェリボム！
Cherry Bomb! Cherry Bomb! Cherry Bomb!
いい？ダメ？
Is it okay? No?
No No No No!
弾けてもっと熟して
Pop and ripen more
どこまでも私を愛して　チェリチェリボム
Love me forever, Cherry Cherry Bomb
弾けてもっと熟してね
Pop and ripen more, okay?
あちゅくちゅく　チェリチェリボム
A-chu-ku-chu-ku, Cherry Cherry Bomb
弾けてもっと熟して
Pop and ripen more
絶対的に私を愛して　チェリチェリボム
Love me absolutely, Cherry Cherry Bomb
弾けてもっと熟してね
Pop and ripen more, okay?
あちゅくちゅく　あちゅくちゅく　あちゅくちゅく　あちゅくちゅく
A-chu-ku-chu-ku, a-chu-ku-chu-ku, a-chu-ku-chu-ku, a-chu-ku-chu-ku
チェリチェリボム
Cherry Cherry Bomb
Cherry cherry bomb
やっぱこの曲さ、3人で歌うのめっちゃいいな
Singing this song with the three of us is really great.
ルーナも好きなのらー
Luna likes it too-nanora.
スバルのさ、「いや、ダメ」のところさ、私とルーナたんに言われて、
When me and Luna-tan teased you during the "No, stop" part,
スバルがガチ照れしてたのめちゃめちゃ可愛かったー
Subaru was seriously blushing and it was so cute!
幸せ恥ずかしがっちゃった可愛いのらねー
She was happily embarrassed, so cute-nanora.
違うよ！うるさい！
That's not it! Shut up!
ということでですね、そんなことよりチョコせん、この後ボタンちゃん待たしてんじゃないの？
Anyway, more importantly, Choco-sen, aren't we making Botan-chan wait after this?
そうやってすぐ話逸らすー
You're changing the subject again.
可愛い...
Cute...
そんなこと言ってないで早く行かないと置いていくぞー
Don't say that, if we don't go quickly, I'll leave you behind!
え、ちょ待ってよスバルー
Wait, hold on Subaru-!
置いていかないで走れないのらー
Don't leave me behind, I can't run-nanora!
ボタンちゃん、お待たせー！
Botan-chan, sorry for the wait!
お待たせー！
Sorry for the wait!
お待たせなのらー！
Sorry for the wait-nanora!
待ってましたよー
I've been waiting.
うわ、3人ともアイドル衣装じゃないですかー。いいなーいいなー
Wow, all three of you are in idol outfits. Nice, nice.
あ、ボタン様だ。あ、そっか、まだお楽しみなのかー
Oh, it's Botan-sama. Ah, I see, yours is still for later.
ちょっとね、お楽しみに待っていただければと思うんですけども
Well, please look forward to it for a bit.
楽しみー！
We're looking forward to it!
せっかくだから私たちもね、通常衣装に着替えませんか？
Since we're here, should we change into our regular outfits too?
あ、本当だ、本当本当
Oh, true, true true.
え、生着替え！？ここで！？
What, a quick change!? Here!?
生着替えのらー！生着替えのらー！
Quick change-nanora! Quick change-nanora!
うるさい、うるさい、うるさい。今から着替えるのらよ
Quiet, quiet, quiet. I'm changing now-nanora.
うるさいって。え、もともと、私たちがいるからちょっと、チョコのためにガチ恋ポーズとか取っててほしいなー
I said quiet. Since we're here, for Choco's sake, I'd like you to do some 'gachi-koi' poses.
え、みんなスクショタイムだぞ、取れ取れ！
Hey, it's screenshot time for everyone, take them, take them!
えー、どうしようかなー。え、じゃあ、こんな感じとかどうです？はい。
Hmm, what should I do... How about something like this? Here.
お待たせー！
Sorry for the wait!
あ、まだあるよ、まだいっぱいあるよ
Oh, there's more, still plenty more.
あ、もう大丈夫、もう大丈夫、ありがとう
Oh, we're good, we're good, thanks.
ごちそうさま。ということで
Thanks for the treat. So...
通常衣装ー！
Regular outfits!
はい、それでは聴いてください。せーの！
Yes, now please listen. One, two-!
ハッピー・ジャムジャム！！
Happy Jam Jam!!
ハッピー・ジャムジャム、イェイ！レッツゴー！
Happy Jam Jam, yay! Let's go!
腰に手を当て　お尻ふりふり　みんなおいでよ　ワンダーランド
Hands on hips, wiggle your butt. Everyone come on to Wonderland.
リズムにのって　1, 2, 3
Get on the rhythm, 1, 2, 3.
ときめき大好き
I love the excitement.
ハッピー・ジャムジャム最高　踊ろうよ　いつもの笑顔で
Happy Jam Jam is the best, let's dance with our usual smiles.
ハッピー・ジャムジャム飛び出そう　ステップ踏めば
Happy Jam Jam, let's jump out. If you take a step...
パラパパパ　パラダイス
Pa-ra-pa-pa-pa paradise!
小さくなって　大きくなって　早く集まれ　ワンダーランド
Become small, become big. Gather quickly in Wonderland.
太陽待ってる　グッドモーニング　きらめき早起き
The sun is waiting, good morning. Sparkling early birds.
ハッピー・ジャムジャム最高　歌おうよ　楽しめメロディ
Happy Jam Jam is the best, let's sing. Enjoy the melody.
ハッピー・ジャムジャム遊ぼうよ　みんな友達
Happy Jam Jam, let's play. Everyone's friends.
パラパパパ　パラダイス
Pa-ra-pa-pa-pa paradise!
ハッピー・ジャムジャム最高　踊ろうよ　いつもの笑顔で
Happy Jam Jam is the best, let's dance with our usual smiles.
ハッピー・ジャムジャム飛び出そう　ステップ踏めば
Happy Jam Jam, let's jump out. If you take a step...
パラパパパ　パラダイス
Pa-ra-pa-pa-pa paradise!
ジャムジャム最高　踊ろうよ　いつもの笑顔で
Jam Jam is the best, let's dance with our usual smiles.
ハッピー・ジャムジャム飛び出そう　ステップ踏めば
Happy Jam Jam, let's jump out. If you take a step...
パラパパパ　パラダイス
Pa-ra-pa-pa-pa paradise!
イェイ　イェイ　イェーイ！
Yay yay yay!
いえーい！ぷえぷーでハッピージャムジャムでしたー！
Yay! That was 'Puepuu de Happy Jamjam'!
いやあ、というか曲のセンスすごすぎた！
Wow, the sense of that song was incredible!
わいわい！ちょこりんにぴったりでしょ？
Waiwai! It's perfect for Choco-rin, right?
まあそれはそうなんだけどね。
Well, that's certainly true.
よかったよかった。
That was great.
あ、せっかくなんでちょっと4人で記念写真撮りましょうよ。
Ah, since we're all here, let's take a commemorative photo.
ルーナ、ルーナ、後ろのサムネポーズ取りたいのら！
Luna, Luna wants to do the thumbnail pose in the back!
いいね！可愛いもんね。
Nice! It's so cute.
みんな並んで並んで！おいで！
Everyone line up, line up! Come here!
こんな感じかしら？
Something like this?
どうだ？どうだ？よいしょ！
How's this? How's this? Heave-ho!
あ、いいねいいね！みんなほら今、スクショ写ショ！
Ah, nice, nice! Everyone, take your screenshots now!
かわよ！ベストショットだったよ！
So cute! That was a best shot!
アップがやばい！早く早く！
The close-up is amazing! Hurry, hurry!
そこにいて！よいしょ！
Stay right there! Heave-ho!
撮った？撮った？大丈夫？可愛い！
Did you get it? Is it okay? So cute!
おしえ！じゃあちょこ先、このあとも頑張ってねマジで。
Alright! Choco-sen, good luck with the rest, seriously.
ありがとー！
Thank you!
えーまだ一緒にいたいのら！
Eh- I still want to stay together!
いたい！
I want to stay!
えーどうしましょう！
Eh- what should we do!
どうしましょうじゃないだろ！ほらもう行くぞ二人とも！
Don't 'what should we do' me! Come on, let's go, you two!
便乗ごっこ！
Tag-along game!
えー！？便乗ごっこ！？
Eh!? Tag-along game!?
スバル先輩早く！
Subaru-senpai, hurry!
え？ご褒美？便乗...
Eh? A reward? Tagging...
便乗便乗！
Tagging along, tagging along!
便乗ごっこか...いいじゃん...いいじゃん...早く進んで！
A tag-along game... fine then... move forward!
早く早く！はい！
Hurry, hurry! Okay!
ありがとー！またねー！
Thank you! See you later!
寄せて寄せて　上げて上げて　ソレソレソレソレ
Squeeze 'em, squeeze 'em, lift 'em, lift 'em, heave-ho!
爆乳音頭
Bakunyuu Ondo (Big Breast Song)
寄せて上げて
Squeeze and lift
谷間作って
Make a cleavage
右乳を飼っています
I'm keeping my right breast as a pet
挟み込んで
Sandwich it in
誘惑して
Tempt them
トリコにしちゃいます
And make them fall for me
熱唱　ハート鷲掴みして
Singing out, grabbing hearts firmly
全てを奪ってしまうかしら
I wonder if I'll steal everything away
お宝　みんな単純な生き物ね
My treasures... everyone is such a simple creature
寄せちゃいな
Squeeze 'em in
揺らしちゃいな
Shake 'em about
大きい方が好きでしょ
You like them big, don't you?
おっぱいおっぱいおっぱい　デカいヤバい　夢いっぱい
Boobs, boobs, boobs! Huge, amazing, full of dreams!
古今東西　老若男女　みんな大好き
Everywhere and everyone, young and old, loves them
パイパー
Pai-paa!
おっぱいおっぱいおっぱい　すごいデカい　見せつけた
Boobs, boobs, boobs! They're so big, I showed them off
乳は千年
Breasts last 1000 years
亀は万年
Turtles last 10000 years
おっぱいだけは　永遠だから
Because boobs alone are eternal
寄せて寄せて　上げて上げて　ソレソレソレソレ
Squeeze 'em, squeeze 'em, lift 'em, lift 'em, heave-ho!
もっといっぱい
You want to see
見たいんでしょ
much more, don't you?
もじもじしてちゃダメ
Don't be so hesitant
頭の中に　焼き付けてみて
Try to burn this image into your mind
思い出してごらん
And just try to remember it
飛び出す　胸で勇気を出して
With these bursting breasts, take courage
世の中　暗い言葉ばかりだから
Since the world is full of dark words
たまには　サービスしちゃってみようかしら
I wonder if I should give a little service sometimes
今日は特別
Today is special
ちょっとはみ出す
Spilling out a little
元気を出して行きましょう
Let's perk up and go!
おっぱいおっぱいおっぱい　デカいヤバい　夢いっぱい
Boobs, boobs, boobs! Huge, amazing, full of dreams!
社長　会長　専務　常務　みんな大好き
Presidents, chairmen, directors, everyone loves them
パイパー
Pai-paa!
おっぱいおっぱいおっぱい　すごいデカい　はち切れそう
Boobs, boobs, boobs! They're so big, they're bursting!
今すぐ　世界を救う
Saving the world right now
宇宙を救う
Saving the universe
それは爆乳　ハードコア
That is the Bakunyuu Hardcore
爆乳爆乳ハードコア
Bakunyuu Bakunyuu Hardcore
パッパッパッパッパッパッパッパッパッパッパッパッパッパッ　爆乳
Pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa Bakunyuu!
パイパー
Pai-paa!
パッパッパッパッパッパッパッパッパッパッパッパッパッパッ　爆乳
Pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa Bakunyuu!
パイパー
Pai-paa!
おっぱいおっぱいおっぱい　デカいヤバい　夢いっぱい
Boobs, boobs, boobs! Huge, amazing, full of dreams!
古今東西　老若男女　みんな大好き
Everywhere and everyone, young and old, loves them
パイパー
Pai-paa!
おっぱいおっぱいおっぱい　すごいデカい　見せつけた
Boobs, boobs, boobs! They're so big, I showed them off
乳は千年
Breasts last 1000 years
亀は万年
Turtles last 10000 years
おっぱいだけは　永遠だから
Because boobs alone are eternal
寄せて寄せて　上げて上げて　ソレソレソレソレ
Squeeze 'em, squeeze 'em, lift 'em, lift 'em, heave-ho!
イェーイ！爆乳！爆乳！
Yeah! Bakunyuu! Bakunyuu!
いやぁ、ちょこ先生、船長の色気で悩殺されちゃったんじゃないですか？
Wow, Choco-sensei, Sencho, didn't you just enchant everyone with your sexiness?
いやぁ、もう！
Oh, my!
いやいやいや、団長も恥ずかしかったけど、この大胸筋見せつけちゃったもんね！
No, no, I was embarrassed too, but I ended up showing off these pectoral muscles!
いやぁ、おごちそうさまでした！ちょこ、この曲歌うのこの連波がいいと思ってめちゃめちゃ楽しみにしてたから！
That was a treat! I've been really looking forward to singing this song with this radio wave!
楽しかったです！
It was fun!
楽しかった！
いや、ていうかさ、これ見てるみんなも、この三人の色気でニヤニヤしてるんじゃないの？！
Well, I bet everyone watching is also grinning at the sexiness of these three!
えー、ちょっと！そんなエロガキいるんですか？
Wait, are there people like that?
もう、しょうがないわね。じゃあ、そんな方にもう少しだけサービスしてあげますわ！
Well, it can't be helped. Shall I give those people a little more service?
もう、しょうがないわね。じゃあ、まずは三人でセクシーポーズでもやります？
It can't be helped. First, why don't the three of us do a sexy pose?
行きますか？はい！
Shall we go? Yes!
じゃあ、こんなのとかどうかしら？シャキーン！
How about something like this? Shakiiin!
いやぁ、かっこいい！セクシー三人衆！エッチだわ。みんなも見ちゃう！
How cool! The Sexy Trio! Everyone's seeing it!
じゃあ、胸とか揺らしてみちゃいます？この曲もそうだったから！
Well, shall we try shaking our chests? This song was like that too.
あー！ブリブリブリブリ……！
Aaaah! Buri buri buri buri...
いやぁ、なんか色売りって感じですね、我々。ホロライブのエロ。
Somehow, we feel like we're selling sexiness. Hololive's Ero.
エロライブ。エロライブ担当ですからね、我々。
Ero-Live. We're in charge of Ero-Live, aren't we?
まあ、こんなところでいいですかね？じゃあ、そろそろエロガキたちもお腹いっぱいになったと思いますので。
Well, is this enough? I think the fans are full now.
おっと！じゃあ、ちょっと、まあ、ちょこ先生はね、まだまだこの後もあるみたいなので、頑張ってください！
Oh? Well, Choco-sensei still has more after this, so please do your best.
ありがとうございます！
Thank you!
じゃあ、まあ、ちょっと、マリンと最後にちょっとあれ言おうか。いい？せーの！
Well, Marine and I have one last thing to say. Ready?
ちょこ先生、お誕生日おめでとうございます！
Choco-sensei, Happy Birthday!
あー！ありがとう！ちょこ、嬉しい！
Aaaah! Thank you! I'm so happy!
じゃあ、さらばだ！
Well then, see ya!
ブリブリブリブリ……！
Buri buri buri buri...
チュチュチュチュ……、トロける魔法で、チュチュチュ、甘くファンシー、チュチュチュ、口どけをもっと、チョコメルティ。
Chu chu chu chu... melting magic, chu chu chu, sweet and fancy, chu chu chu, melt-in-your-mouth more, Choco Melty.
はい！はい！はい！……、よーし、いくぞー！
Hai! Hai! Hai! ... Here we go!
ほんの少しお疲れな日は、幸せの箱開けちゃおう。
On those slightly tiring days, let's open the box of happiness.
甘いその誘惑も、乗ってみるの？
The sweet temptation, let's try riding it.
お疲れ様です！乾杯！
Good job! Cheers!
二つか三つ、強気にねハート、もっともっと好きになってね。
Two or three, get stronger in your heart, fall in love more and more.
不器用だけど愛して、さあ、みんなで！
Even if you're clumsy, just love. Everyone together!
ちょこ先生、お誕生日おめでとう！
Choco-sensei, Happy Birthday!
メル様ありがとう！ちょこ嬉しい！
Mel-sama, thank you! I'm so happy!
プレゼントはメルだよ！
My present is Mel!
ガチ？え、それとお触りありですか？あ、もうほら！
Wait, is it okay to touch? Oh, look!
私たちと踊りましょう！
Let's dance with us!
今日も明日も、メルメルメルティハート。
Today and tomorrow, Mel-Mel-Melty heart.
チョコとキャラメル、召し上がれ、笑顔で彩りを。
Choco and caramel, have some. Decorate with a smile.
ずっと付いてきて、サニーラッキーな日々を。
Stay with me forever, Sunny-Lucky days.
君と見つめ合う未来で、さあ、よろしくどうぞ！
With the future where we look at each other, nice to meet you!
チュチュチュ、トロける魔法で、チュチュチュ、甘くファンシー、チュチュチュ、ちょっと苦い、チョコメルティ。
Chu chu chu... melting magic, chu chu chu, sweet and fancy, chu chu chu, a bit bitter, Choco Melty.
はい！はい！はい！……、よーし、いくぞー！
Hai! Hai! Hai! ... Here we go!
あ、ひと休みしていいかな、頑張りすぎも毒だし。
It's okay to feel a little sick, being too hard-working is poison.
苦くも甘い誘惑も、受け入れてみてね。
Accept the bitter and sweet temptation.
ご苦労様です！ほら！
Good job! Here!
見てあげるわ君のハート、ほんのちょっと照れくさいかな？
I'll show you, your heart, are you a bit embarrassed?
私たちだけを愛して、さあ、みんなで！
Just love me. Everyone together!
ねえメル様、今日バレンタインなの知ってる？
Hey, Mel-sama, do you know today is Valentine's?
もちろん！チョコもらいたいするの？
Of course! Do you want some chocolate?
メル様にはチョコ手作り用意したわよ！
I prepared handmade chocolate for Mel-sama!
本当？！メルも作ろうかな！
Really? Maybe I'll make some too!
いいえ、それは大丈夫です！なんでよー！
No, no, that's okay! Why?!
私たちとはしゃぎましょう！
Let's have fun with us!
いつもいつまでも、メルメルメルティハート。
Always and forever, Mel-Mel-Melty heart.
チョコレートココア召し上がれ、いたずらな……
Chocolate and cocoa, have some, mischievous...
レシピを
The recipe
もっと
more
ついてきて
follow me
ハッピーラッキーな日々も
Even happy lucky days
ボリュームいっぱいの未来見て
Looking at a full-volume future
さあ ずっと続くよ
Come on, it goes on forever
ここに居れることがただただ嬉しくて
I'm just so happy to be able to be here
この大切な時間が止まって欲しくて
I want this precious time to stop
あなたに出会えた事も
The fact that I met you
あなたに見つけてもらえた事も
The fact that you found me
甘くて淡い最高の出会いを
The sweet and faint best encounter
両手広げて
Spread both hands
胸に抱きしめて
Hold close to your chest
最高な笑顔で
With the best smile
ワクワクキラキラドキドキ全て手にして
Take all the excitement and sparkle in your hands
もしもこの夢が叶うとするのなら
If this dream were to come true
幸せの形作って
Making the shape of happiness
ビターでもシュガーでも
Whether bitter or sugary
今日も明日も
Today and tomorrow too
メリーメルティな恋とな
A merry melty love
チョコとキャラメル召し上がれ
Please enjoy the chocolate and caramel
好きなどのモノ物語りを
A story of likes and such
ずっとついてきて
Follow me forever
ハッピーラッキーな日々を
Happy lucky days
君と見つめ合う未来で
In a future where we gaze at each other
さあ よろしくどうぞ
Now, nice to meet you
チュチュチュ ちょっと焦燥
Chu chu chu, a bit impatient
チュチュチュ 甘えん坊
Chu chu chu, a spoiled child
チュチュチュ ちょっと苦い
Chu chu chu, a bit bitter
あー！ チュチュチュ
Ah! Chu chu chu
チュチュチュ 夢メロメロ
Chu chu chu, madly in love in dreams
チュチュチュ 新規ドキ
Chu chu chu, heartbeat for someone new
チュチュチュ 口溶けチョコメロディ
Chu chu chu, melting chocolate melody
イェーイ！
Yay!
はい！ということで メルティスのオリ曲「Choco♡Melty」でしたー！
Yes! So that was Melty's original song 'Choco♡Melty'!
イェーイ！フゥー！
Yay! Woo!
いや 皆様 聞いてくれてありがとうございます！
Wow, thank you everyone for listening!
ありがとうみんな！
Thank you everyone!
楽しかったー！
That was fun!
いやめちゃくちゃ楽しかったね！
Yeah, it was really fun!
チョコ先生 お誕生日おめでとう！
Choco-sensei, happy birthday!
メル様 ありがとうー！
Mel-sama, thank you!
あの 今日チョコ お誕生日だから ちょっとメル様に プレゼントもらいたいな…なんて…
Um, since it's Choco's birthday today, I was thinking I might want a present from Mel-sama... maybe...
何でもあげちゃうよ！
I'll give you anything!
何でも？ 何でもいいの？
Anything? Is anything okay?
何でもいいよ。
Anything is fine.
本当に？ガチ？言ってみ 言ってみ。
Really? For real? Say it, say it.
じゃ…じゃあ…
Then... then...
チョコ ずっとうらやましいと思ってたことがあって。
there's something Choco has always been envious of.
何？
What is it?
カプ民のみんなにしてるように、チョコにも…カプッ…カプッ…してほしいな…なんて…
Like you do for all the Kapu-min, I want you to... go 'kapu'... 'kapu' for Choco too... maybe...
あー！ そんなんでいいの？しちゃうよー。
Ah! Is that all? I'll do it!
いいの？いいの？本当に？
Is it okay? Is it okay? Really?
ちょっと改めてやると なると緊張するね。
Doing it formally like this makes me nervous.
よし。いくよ？
Alright. Ready?
チョコ先生 大好き。カプッ。
Choco-sensei, I love you. *Kapu*.
あー！ありがとうございます メル様！
Ah! Thank you Mel-sama!
チョコ 幸せー！
Choco is so happy!
チョコ先生 生まれてきてくれてありがとう。
Choco-sensei, thank you for being born.
これからもよろしくね。
Let's keep being friends.
このあとも頑張ってね！
Good luck with the rest of the show!
あー ありがとうメル様ー！
Ah, thank you Mel-sama!
またねー！バイバイー！
See you! Bye-bye!
出会いと別れ 繰り返すたび
Every time meetings and partings repeat,
心を擦り減らす
my heart wears down
記憶をかき分けた先に
Beyond where I searched through my memories,
滲んだ思い出が
blurred recollections...
あなたを知らない 世界のほうが
A world without knowing you
ずっとマシだったと笑う
would have been much better, I laugh
いつしか すれ違う日々の中で
At some point, in the days where we passed each other by,
本音隠しながら
while hiding my true feelings...
気づかないふり
Pretending not to notice,
茜色の この街眺めては
looking out at this madder-red town...
こんなにも あなたのこと
I'm just so much about you...
思い出してばかり
...doing nothing but remembering you
忘れたいのに 今更素直になれない
Although I want to forget, I can't be honest now.
分かってたんだよ
I knew it.
今も心は泣いてるよ
Even now, my heart is crying.
季節を越えて
Beyond the seasons,
あなたはまた
you again
世界を奪っていく
take away my world.
感じる温もりが
The warmth I feel
そっと私の未来も
gently takes away my future too.
奪う
Takes it away.
時計の針は
The clock hands
突然止まる
suddenly stop
あなたが告げた言葉で
at the words you told me.
どうしてここで一人なんだろう
Why am I alone here?
流した涙の意味を
The meaning of the tears I shed,
ねえ教えてよ
hey, tell me.
二人でいたこの道歩いても
Even if I walk this path where we were together,
もう二度とあなたのこと
I will never
思い出しはしない
think of you again.
忘れるように 愛した証を脱ぎ捨てて
Casting aside the proof of my love to forget,
また新しい日々へと歩き出す
I'll start walking into new days again.
細かく破れた手紙を
The finely torn letter...
結んだ髪をほどいて
Unbinding my tied-up hair,
悲しみから解き放つために叫んだ
I screamed to set myself free from sadness.
優しくなれる心が欲しいよ
I want a heart that can become kind.
凍えそうだよ 寂しさ嘆いても
I feel like I'm freezing, even if I lament the loneliness.
大好きで大嫌いなあなたはもういない
You, whom I love and hate so much, are no longer here.
巻き戻してあの日に戻れるのならば
If I could rewind and go back to that day,
伝えたいけど今も遅いかな
I'd want to tell you, but is it too late now?
赤色のこの街眺めては
Looking at this crimson town,
こんなにもあなたのこと 思い出してばかり
I'm only thinking about you this much.
忘れたいのに 今更素直になれない
Although I want to forget, I can't be honest now.
分かってたんだよ
I knew it.
ずっとあなたを求めてた
I've been searching for you all along.
はい！ということで、月見草でしたー！
Yes! So that was "Tsukimisou"!
いや、実はちょこ、初めて3D配信でバラード歌っちゃって、
Actually, it's Choco's first time singing a ballad in a 3D stream,
ちょっと内心めちゃくちゃなんかドキドキしてるんだけど、
so deep down I'm really nervous, but,
ねえどうだった？どうだったー？
hey, how was it? How was it?
ちょっと恥ずかしい。
It's a bit embarrassing.
ありがとう！んー、優しい。好き！
Thank you! Mm, you're so kind. I love you!
ということで、ここで重大告知がありまーす！
So, I have a major announcement here!
まず一つ目！
First one!
なななななんと！
Wh-wh-wh-what?!
癒月ちょこ誕生日記念グッズがこの後21時から発売開始されまーす！
Yuzuki Choco birthday commemorative goods will go on sale from 9 PM after this!
今回のグッズはこちら！
Here are the goods for this time!
ダダダダーン！
Ta-da!
まず一つ目は、皆様お待たせいたしました！
First, the one you've all been waiting for!
Nardack先生描き下ろし、癒月ちょこ抱き枕カバー！
Illustrated by Nardack-sensei, the Yuzuki Choco Dakimakura Cover!
いや、こちらね、なんと両面ございまして、
This one, actually, is double-sided,
それではちょっと、ベッドでちょこが寝落ちしてる感じのやつで、
Well, it's like Choco has fallen asleep in bed...
で、裏面がなんと、帰ってきましたホロライブサマー！
And for the back side, guess what, Hololive Summer is back!
ということで、ちょこの水着衣装で、
So, it features Choco in her swimsuit costume,
背中にね、ちょっとね、オイル塗ってもらう絵になっております。
it's an illustration where you're putting some oil on my back.
そして2つ目は、ラーメンどんぶり！
And the second item is... a ramen bowl!
いや最近ね、ちょこTwitterのスペースやってるんですけど、
Recently, I've been doing Twitter Spaces,
そこで、あの深夜に、あの飯テロラーメン枠をよく、なんか恒例化してて、
and there, late at night, I've been doing these 'food porn' ramen streams quite regularly.
まあね、皆様もね、ぜひ、ちょことお揃いのどんぶりで深夜に罪の味を味わってみてはいかがでしょうか！
So, everyone, why don't you taste the flavor of sin late at night with a bowl that matches Choco's!
なんとこれ、全部食べ終わるとね、なんとそこにむーらん先生描き下ろし、
Actually, when you finish eating everything, there's an illustration by Mooran-sensei...
ちょこの、つまえ、あ、間違えた。スカイパパの、ちょこらがちょっとね、満腹姿で、
of Choco... wait, I mean, Skypapa's Chocola in a satisfied, full state...
現れるのでね、ぜひぜひ完食して癒されてください。
will appear, so please finish the meal and be healed.
そして3つ目！
And the third item!
癒月ちょこ ASMR ボイス！
Yuzuki Choco ASMR Voice!
ということで今回はグッズ記念で、ぜひ抱き枕をね、抱きながら、あの、聴いてほしい、
This time, to commemorate the goods, I want you to listen to it while hugging the dakimakura.
ギュッとしてっていう、心音、吐息入りのボイス。そして、
Voices of heartbeats and breathing, like a 'hug me' moment. And...
深夜ラーメンを食べるときに聴いてほしい、悪魔の味は罪の味、耳舐めボイス！
an ear-licking voice meant to be heard while eating late-night ramen, 'The taste of a demon is the taste of sin!'
いやこちらはね、特典ボイスとなっております。そして、
These are special bonus voices. And...
ちょこねお誕生日にこのボイスね、ずっと出したかったの。
I've wanted to release these voices on my birthday for a long time.
今回出しちゃいます！ということで、
I'm releasing them this time! So,
ちょこ先生がお誕生日を祝ってくれる、耳舐め ASMR ボイス！
Choco-sensei celebrates her birthday with an ear-licking ASMR voice!
さらにさらに、全部セットご購入の方のみ、
Furthermore, only for those who purchase the full set,
癒月ちょこ直筆サイン入りポストカードが、今回、全員にサイン書いちゃいます、ちょこ！
there's a postcard with Yuzuki Choco's handwritten signature... I'll be signing them for everyone this time!
いやね、全員はちょっと数年…限定じゃなくて、全員はめちゃめちゃ久しぶりなんですけど、
It's been a very long time since I've signed for everyone, not just a limited number.
ぜひぜひ皆様、ちょこの直筆サイン欲しくないですか？
So, everyone, don't you want Choco's handwritten signature?
今回はね、ちょこ頑張って全員に書くので、ぜひぜひ全部セットもよろしくお願いします。
I'll do my best to sign for everyone this time, so please check out the full set as well.
ということで今回運営さんにね、今、概要欄にグッズの URL 貼っていただいたので、
The staff has just put the URL for the goods in the description,
ぜひぜひ更新して、こちらね 21時からサイトオープンとなりますので、
so please refresh it. The site opens at 21:00,
皆様待機よろしくお願いします！
so please be ready and waiting!
ということで、それでは、重大告知2つ目はこのあとすぐ！最後までお見逃しなく！
And now, the second major announcement is coming right up! Stay tuned until the very end!
好きですか？の中身に
Do you like it? Inside that...
笑顔で返すしかできない
I can only respond with a smile
まるで悪魔に飼われたように
As if being kept by a demon
私の答えを君は待っている
You are waiting for my answer
放課後の教室に
In the classroom after school
君だけを残す時間が好き
I like the time when only you are left
二人きりになっても
Even if we are alone together
許される場所になるでしょう ねぇ
It will become a place where it's allowed, right?
きっとあの子のように隣を歩けないのは
The reason I surely can't walk beside you like that girl
待つ背中に揺れる白衣
Is the white coat swaying on my waiting back
それが二人の距離だから
Because that is the distance between us
熱くなるほど幼い
The hotter it gets, the more childish
心がバレちゃわないように
So that my heart isn't found out
君にとっての大人になるフリをして似合う
I'll pretend to be the adult that suits you
秘密のクラス
A secret class
好きですか？の中身に
Do you like it? Inside that...
笑顔で返すしかできない
I can only respond with a smile
まるで悪魔に飼われたように
As if being kept by a demon
私の答えを君は待っている
You are waiting for my answer
甘い恋に仕立てて
Tailored into a sweet love
アルバムにしてあげたほうがいい
It would be better to put it in an album
終わりを告げるチャイムが
The chime that announces the end
いつ鳴るかそれがたまらなく怖い
I'm irresistibly scared of when it will ring
とあの子のほうが君に似合いだなんて
That she's a better match for you...
猿芝居と揺れる白衣
The charade and the swaying lab coat.
ふとした言葉も傷つけてしまう
Even casual words end up hurting.
失うものなど何もない
There is nothing left to lose.
無邪気な目で苦しめないで
Don't torture me with those innocent eyes.
君のテストに大人さえも答えられない
Even an adult can't answer your tests.
言葉に詰まる　好きだよと
I'm at a loss for words, saying "I love you"...
全部捨てて抱き寄せてしまいたいのに
Though I want to throw it all away and hold you close.
そんな強い心じゃいられない
I can't maintain such a strong heart.
私の答えに罰をつけて
Give my answer a failing mark.
これでいい　君のために
This is fine, it's for your sake.
そう決めたのに
Even though I decided so.
猿芝居なびく白衣
The charade, the fluttering lab coat.
思わず君を引き止める
I reflexively stop you.
好きですか　の難題に
To the difficult question, "Do you love me?"
許されない答えを書いた
I wrote an unforgivable answer.
君の明日を縛るだけの独りよがりな
A self-centered promise of love
恋の約束
that only binds your tomorrow.
ただ君の悲しむ顔
If I just don't have to see...
もう見送らなくていいなら
...your sad face anymore.
たとえ悪魔と呼ばれてもいい
I don't care if I'm called a demon.
甘く蕩けるようなひと時をあなたに
I'll give you a moment that melts sweetly.
ということで、重大告知その2は！
And so, important announcement number two is!
今歌ったちょこの新曲！
The new song I just sang!
奏音69先生書き下ろし、Secret Classでしたー！
It was "Secret Class" written by Kanon69!
いやちょこ、奏音69様のね、曲めちゃくちゃ好きで、
I really love Kanon69-sama's music,
まさかの作詞作曲書き下ろしされると思ってなくて、本当にちょこめちゃめちゃ感激しちゃった！
and I never thought he'd write one for me, so I'm truly touched!
そしてなんとこの後、21時からMV公開、
And, believe it or not, the MV will be out at 21:00,
そして楽曲配信が始まるので、ぜひぜひ皆さん概要欄のURLからね、
and the digital release will start, so please check the link in the description,
いっぱい聞いてみてください！
and listen to it many times!
それでは、最後までご視聴、誠にありがとうございました！
Well then, thank you so much for watching until the very end!
みんな大好き、おつかれとー！
I love you all! Otsukare-to!